(this["webpackJsonpreact-challenge"]=this["webpackJsonpreact-challenge"]||[]).push([[0],{1:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F","correct_answer":"Dirk%20the%20Daring","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","Sir%20Toby%20Belch","Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F","correct_answer":"Homo%20Sapiens","incorrect_answers":["Homo%20Ergaster","Homo%20Erectus","Homo%20Neanderthalensis"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Books","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F","correct_answer":"Bilius","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","John","Dominic"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F","correct_answer":"Robert%20Kirkman","incorrect_answers":["Stan%20Lee","Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert%20Crumb"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F","correct_answer":"Electric%20Company","incorrect_answers":["Water%20Works","Chance","Community%20Chest"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F","correct_answer":"Kingston","incorrect_answers":["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Dar%20es%20Salaam","Kano"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20","correct_answer":"1962","incorrect_answers":["1492","1963","1987"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.","incorrect_answers":["True"],"correct_answer":"False"},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F","correct_answer":"%2412.7%20Billion","incorrect_answers":["%2495%20Million","%24956%20Million","%242.7%20Billion"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F","correct_answer":"55","incorrect_answers":["50","60","54"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F","correct_answer":"Alonsus%20Faol","incorrect_answers":["Uther%20the%20Lightbringer","Alexandros%20Mograine","Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.","incorrect_answers":["False"],"correct_answer":"True"},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F","correct_answer":"Coils","incorrect_answers":["Wires","Collectors","Tesla"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F","correct_answer":"Vanilla","incorrect_answers":["Peach","Strawberry","Mint"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.","correct_answer":"Poland%20and%20Lithuania","incorrect_answers":["Hutu%20and%20Rwanda","North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea","Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Television","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F","correct_answer":"George%20Clooney","incorrect_answers":["Matthew%20Perry","Dennis%20Miller","Pierce%20Brosnan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F","correct_answer":"Plastic%20Beach","incorrect_answers":["Demon%20Days","Humanz","The%20Fall"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.","incorrect_answers":["True"],"correct_answer":"False"},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F","correct_answer":"No%20Mercy","incorrect_answers":["Subway%20Sprint","Hospital%20Havoc","Blood%20Harvest"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F","correct_answer":"Hong%20Kong","incorrect_answers":["India","Australia","Ireland"]}]')},13:function(e,t,r){},15:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var n=r(2),a=r.n(n),s=r(4),o=r.n(s),i=(r(13),r(5)),c=r(6),l=r(8),d=r(7),u=r(1),h=r(0),m=function(e){Object(l.a)(r,e);var t=Object(d.a)(r);function r(){var e;Object(i.a)(this,r);for(var n=arguments.length,a=new Array(n),s=0;s<n;s++)a[s]=arguments[s];return(e=t.call.apply(t,[this].concat(a))).state={score:0,count:0,progress:5,attempted:0},e.onAnswerSelect=function(t){var r=e.state,n=r.count,a=r.score,s=r.attempted,o=document.querySelectorAll(".options"),i=1/u.length*100;e.setState({attempted:s+1});for(var c=0;c<o.length;c++)o[c].disabled=!0;t===decodeURIComponent(u[n].correct_answer)?(e.setState({score:a+i}),n+1===20?document.getElementById("output").innerHTML="<h2>Correct!</h2><h2>Quiz Completed!</h2>":(document.getElementById("output").innerHTML="<h2>Correct!</h2>",document.getElementById("next").style.display="block")):n+1===20?document.getElementById("output").innerHTML="<h2>Incorrect!</h2><h2>Quiz Completed!</h2>":(document.getElementById("output").innerHTML="<h2>Incorrect!</h2>",document.getElementById("next").style.display="block")},e.nextQuestion=function(){var t=e.state,r=t.count,n=t.progress,a=document.querySelectorAll(".options");e.setState({count:++r}),document.getElementById("next").style.display="none",document.getElementById("output").innerHTML="";for(var s=0;s<a.length;s++)a[s].disabled=!1;e.setState({progress:n+5}),r+1===20?document.getElementById("next").disabled=!0:document.getElementById("output").innerHTML=""},e}return Object(c.a)(r,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this,t=this.state,r=t.count,n=t.score,a=t.progress,s=t.attempted,o=1/u.length*100,i=u.length-s;i=i*o+n;var c=n/100*100,l=u[r].incorrect_answers.concat(u[r].correct_answer);return Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"container",children:[Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"card",children:[Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"card-header",children:[Object(h.jsxs)("h2",{children:["Question ",r+1," of ",u.length]}),Object(h.jsx)("h6",{children:decodeURIComponent(u[r].category)}),"hard"===u[r].difficulty?Object(h.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(h.jsx)("i",{class:"fas fa-star"}),Object(h.jsx)("i",{class:"fas fa-star"}),Object(h.jsx)("i",{class:"fas fa-star"}),Object(h.jsx)("i",{class:"far fa-star"}),Object(h.jsx)("i",{class:"far fa-star"})]}):(u[r].difficulty,Object(h.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(h.jsx)("i",{class:"fas fa-star"}),Object(h.jsx)("i",{class:"fas fa-star"}),Object(h.jsx)("i",{class:"far fa-star"}),Object(h.jsx)("i",{class:"far fa-star"}),Object(h.jsx)("i",{class:"far fa-star"})]}))]}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{class:"progress",children:Object(h.jsx)("div",{class:"progress-bar bg-secondary",style:{width:a+"%"}})}),Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"card-body",children:[Object(h.jsx)("p",{children:Object(h.jsx)("b",{children:decodeURIComponent(u[r].question)})}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"row",children:l.map((function(t){return u[r].type,Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"col-md-3",children:Object(h.jsx)("button",{className:"btn btn-dark options",value:decodeURIComponent(t),type:"submit",onClick:function(){return e.onAnswerSelect(decodeURIComponent(t))},children:decodeURIComponent(t)})})}))}),Object(h.jsx)("br",{}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{id:"output"}),Object(h.jsx)("button",{id:"next",style:{display:"none"},className:"btn btn-dark",onClick:this.nextQuestion,type:"submit",children:"Next"})]}),Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"card-footer",children:[Object(h.jsxs)("h5",{style:{textAlign:"left"},children:["Score: ",n,"%"]}),Object(h.jsxs)("h5",{style:{textAlign:"right"},children:["Max Score: ",i,"%"]}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"row",children:Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"col-md-12",children:Object(h.jsxs)("div",{class:"progress",children:[Object(h.jsx)("div",{class:"progress-bar bg-dark",style:{width:c+"%"}}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{class:"progress-bar bg-secondary",style:{width:n+"%"}}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{class:"progress-bar bg-light",style:{width:i+"%"}})]})})})]})]}),Object(h.jsx)("br",{})]})}}]),r}(n.Component);var y=function(){return Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"App",children:Object(h.jsx)("header",{className:"App-header",children:Object(h.jsx)(m,{})})})},f=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&r.e(3).then(r.bind(null,16)).then((function(t){var r=t.getCLS,n=t.getFID,a=t.getFCP,s=t.getLCP,o=t.getTTFB;r(e),n(e),a(e),s(e),o(e)}))};o.a.render(Object(h.jsx)(a.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(h.jsx)(y,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),f()}},[[15,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.c2048828.chunk.js.map